HECTOR MARTINEZ

Software developer

https://github.com/Thornnk

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/hector-md | M hnezado@gmail.com

With nearly four years immersed in programming, I've cultivated a fusion of logic and creativity that fuels my problem-solving skills. I excel within collaborative teams, contributing both initiative and passion for innovative solutions to drive project success.

WORK EXPERIENCE

May 2023 - Dic 2023 **Qaracter - BBVAIT**

Business Analyst

Development new features and fixes for the bulk data ingestion processes within the Recovery Management platform at BBVAIT.

Cobol, JCL, Batch chains, IBM 3270 - Mainframe

Feb 2022 - Sep 2022 Sistrol S.A.

Software developer

Development of smart building data tools, integrating them into the overall data infrastructure. Automatization tasks, streamlining my team's workflow.

Python, Git/Github, AWS, Linux, Docker, SkySpark

Sep 2021 - Dec 2021 Setorium (Bootcamp Project)

Data scientist

Python, Selenium, Tensorflow, Keras, OpenCV, Flask, HTML,

CSS, lavascript

Mar 2021 - May 2021 Applant, Alloy me app, To Eat or not To Eat

(Bootcamp project)

Full-stack developer

Javascript, HTML, CSS, Canvas, Bootstrap, MongoDB, Node|S,

API, React, SASS

Nov 2020 - Feb 2021 **RYME Worldwide**

> Administrative assistant Office, Photoshop, SAP, C#

EDUCATION

Mar 2023 - May 2023 **Cobol – Finances Course**

Grupo Loyal – Qaracter Academy

Apr 2022 **Linux Introduction**

edX

Sep 2021 - Dec 2021 Data Science, Machine Learning & Al

Id Bootcamps

Mar 2021 - May 2021 Full-stack web development

Ironhack



LANGUAGES

Spanish Native English French A2 Japanese

SKILLS

Python Javascript MongoDB MySQL Docker AWS React Flask Pandas ML/IA

HTML & CSS Cobol ICL

(# Linux IIRA

INTERESTS

- Computer Science
- Technology / Space
- Travelling
- Languages
- Mountaineering
- Scuba-diving